Adams, Leonard P. Papers /3046
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Leonard P. Adams Papers
1949-1967
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Adams, Leonard P.
/3046
35.5 cubic feet
35 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Study of what happened in Auburn, New York when the International Harvester Company closed its plant.
7924613
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 21, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 08, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4008: Leonard P. Adams Additional Files
Adams, Leonard P.
7924613
- Student Interview Questionnaires, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Student Interview Questionnaires, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Check Totals- Auburn Study: Layoff, Quit, and Cross-Section, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Revised Chapters VII-IX Auburn, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Auburn: Second Carbon of Revised Chapters, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Auburn Study: Memorandums, Dispositions, and Hypotheses, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Carbon of Draft, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Chapter I: Read- no corrections, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Chapter I: Characteristics of Samples, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Auburn Study: Chapter I Introduction, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Chapter II: Characteristics of Local Labor Market, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Chapter III- corrected, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Chapter III- Patterns of Mobility, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Auburn Study- Chapter III Displacement and its Consequences, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Auburn- Chapter IV, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Chapter IV, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Auburn Study- Chapter IV Softening the Impact of Industrial Change, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Chapter IV Corrected and Carbon Uncorrected, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Chapter V: Read- no corrections, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Chapter V, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Chapter V- Auburn Study, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Chapter V- Job Seeking and Reemployment, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Chapter V, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO Symposium: Reuther, Walter P. "Unity of Labor." Chapter VI, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Chapter VI- Job Satisfactions, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Chapter VI: High School Study- Prelim. Report, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Auburn Study- Chapter VI: Affects of Job Satisfaction and Labor Mobility, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Chapter VI, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Chapter VII: Unemployment Insurance and State Employment Service, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Auburn Study: Chapter VII, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Auburn Revised Chapter VIII, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Chapter VII- Youth Job Market and Occupation Choice, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Original Corrections, Chapters VII-IX, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Chapter VIII- Education, 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Auburn Study- Chapter VIII Entrance into the Labor Market, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Chapter IX, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Chapter IX- Unemployment Insurance and Comm. Resources, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Chapter X- Worker Perspectives on Industrial Change, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Auburn Study Chapter IX (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Chapter X, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Auburn Study- Chapter X Labor Mobility in the Long-Run, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Draft Auburn, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Chapter10- Findings and Conclusion, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Auburn Study Chapter XII, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Auburn Study- Chapter XII, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Appendix B Proofread and Corrected, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Auburn study Surveys, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Auburns Study Surveys, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Bureau of Labor Statistics Personal Interview Questionnaires and Classification Cards, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Research Proposals, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Selected Bibliography Index Cards (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Bureau of Public Roads, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Herkimer--Otsego Counties, N.Y., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Indiana, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Ithaca, N.Y., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Johnstown, Pa., 1948-1951 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Monroe County, N.Y., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Oneida, New York, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Odessa, N.Y, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Philadelphia, and surrounding area Post War, 1948-1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Schuyler County, N.Y., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Rural Connecticut, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- World War II- Drafts of Part I of Report, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Drafts Part II, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Part 3 Drafts, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Central Correspondence- Housing Research Center, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- General Accounting, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Payroll, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Travel Vouchers, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Monthly Progress Report (Housing Research Center), 1952 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Expense, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Proposal and Contracts, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Personnel, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Commuting Patterns of Industrial Workers, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- 1955 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Worker's Residences, By Country, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Journey to Work Revision, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- General Data, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Essential Wartime Staggering of Hours, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Journey To Work Letters and Replies, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Journey to Work Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Publications- Memos, Forms, Corres., ect., 1947-1949 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- "Journey to Work" Data and Memos, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Auburn Study Surveys, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- IH Questionnaires- Returns, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Auburn Study- Memorandums and Drafts, 1953-1955 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Auburn- Old Version Revised Chapters, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- I.H. Questionnaire Sample (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Material On The Withdrawal Of The International Harvester Co. From Auburn, N.Y. And The Resultant Community Activities As Reported In The Auburn Citizen-Advertiser, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Buffalo Study- Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- "Wartime Manpower Mobilization" Draft, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Buffalo Study Appendix, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Clippings, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Draft 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Draft 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Pamphlets, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Strikes and Lockouts, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Releases (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Buffalo Manpower Mobilization Study Card File, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- The Journey to Work: A Guide for Delineating Labor and Housing Supply Areas for Defense Plants, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- World War II Data By Cities, 1942-1951 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- 1951 Survey (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Questionnaire, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Auburn Study- Cross Sections and Articles, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Auburn Study- Data for Next to Last Chapter (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Auburn Labor Market Data, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Auburn Study- Chapter VII Revisions (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Auburn Study Outlines (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Auburn Study Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Auburn Background Data, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Job History (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Auburn- Chamber of Commerce, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Auburn- Company and Union Documents, 1945-1949 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Auburn Field Notes (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Cayuga City, Labor Force Est., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- High School Study- Interviews, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- IH Mail Questionnaire- Tallies, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- I.H. Pensioners, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- I.H. Sample- Laid-off Contacted, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Auburn- Labor Organizations, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Auburn Study- Sample Adequacy, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- MasterTransportation Code (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Research: The Industrial Development of Auburn (Seymour Parker's Article) (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Auburn- Schedules, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Auburn- Home Relief, 1949-1951 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- A Terminations Due to Plant Closing Previously Laid-Off, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- A&B I.H. Sample To Be Contacted, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Voluntary Terminations, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Other Labor Mobility Studies, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Auburn Study Interview Samples (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Auburn Study Interview Samples (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Stabilization Foundries, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Buffalo Area Field Reports, 1941-1945 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Priority Referrals, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- 3-11K - Must Company Reports, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Stabilization: Women in Foundries, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Controlled Referral, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Controlled Referral, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- E-11E - N "Weekly Progress" Reports, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Stabilization: Correspondence re Ceilings, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- #3-11 L - "Blackboard" Company Reports, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Blank Interview Questions and Coding Instructions (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Manpower: Louisville Plan, Handbook, and Confidential Information of Area Directors, 1942-1944 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Buffalo, N. Tonawanoa, Niagara Falls, and Lockport Referrals and Placements, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Manpower Reports, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Labor Market Reports: Buffalo, N. Falls, Lockport, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Joint Legislation Committee on the State's Economy, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Employment Trends, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- ILR Research Publication, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Preliminary Draft Not for Publication, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Establishments Covered By Unemployment Insurance By Industry, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Establishments Covered By Unemployment Insurance By Industry, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- A Report on The Changing Structure of Industrial Employment in New York State, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- A Report on The Changing Structure of Industrial Employment in New York State, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Data on Employment of School Leavers, 1951-1956 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Data on Employment of Disabled School Leavers, 1953-1956 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Youth in Job Market Study- Dropout Cards, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Youth in Job Market Study- Graduates Cards, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Youth in Job Market Study- Graduates Cards and Category 3, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Dropouts Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Youth in the Job Market: Dropout Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Blank Dropout Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Blank Dropout Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Blank Dropout Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Computer Punch Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Computer Punch Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Computer Punch Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Graduates Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Graduates Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Blank Graduates Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Blank Graduates Cards, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Industrial Development, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Graduates Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Graduates Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Graduates Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Graduates Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Graduates Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Graduates Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Graduates Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Graduates Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Dropout Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Dropout Personal Interview Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Injury to Family Members of School-Leaves No Longer Living in Utica Area, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Injury to Family Members of School-Leaves No Longer Living in Utica Area, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Injury to Family Members of School-Leaves No Longer Living in Utica Area, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Injury to Family Members of School-Leaves No Longer Living in Utica Area, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire Military Service, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire Military Service, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Personal Interview Questionnaire Military Service, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Instructions for Interviews, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Completed Interviews (Schedules A and B), 1957 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Blank Schedule B Interview Questionnaires, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Blank Schedule B Interview Questionnaires, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Blank Schedule B Interview Questionnaires, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Blank Schedule B Interview Questionnaires, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Youth in the Job Market Study Interviews: Continued Education, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Youth in the Job Market Study Interviews: Continued Education, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Youth in the Job Market Study Interviews: Continued Education, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Youth in the Job Market Study Interviews: Out Migrants, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Youth in the Job Market Study Interviews: Out of Sample and Others, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Youth in the Job Market Study Interviews: Out of Sample and Others`, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Youth in the Job Market Study: Comparative Study and Union Agreement, 1957-1961 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- ILR Research Department, 1945-1948 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Proposed research project, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Reports of consultants on future policy and programming of the federal-state employment service. Drafts of report and correspondence., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Correspondence. Public employment service research project., 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Public employment service. Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- The place of employment service, rough draft of paper, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Connecticut- correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- New Haven, Connecticut- research data, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- New Haven, Connecticut- research data, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Connecticut. Labor Dept.- Reports, newsletters, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Connecticut. Labor Dept. Monthly Bulletin, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Employment agencies and the labor marketing process in the New Haven, Conn. Area, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Wisconsin State Employment Service- research studies reports, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Wisconsin- Activities of employment service, 1948-1961 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Wisconsin- History of employment service (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Wisconsin- Private agencies, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Wisconsin- Professional placement, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Wisconsin- contracts, 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Wisconsin- Statistical Dept. Employment and wages covered by Wisconsin U.C. law, 1954-1961 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Wisconsin- Employment data, 1950-1962 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Employment agencies and labor market process in the Milwaukee, Wis. Area. Draft of paper., 1962 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Wisconsin- correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Milwaukee- Employment Service Operations, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- New York City- correspondence, data, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Rochester- Personal notes and data, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Rochester- Study of employment practices- data, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Rochester- Study of employment practices- draft of study, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Ithaca- Study of employment practices data, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Ithaca- Study of employment practices data, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Draft of Elmira Study, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Elmira Study Data, 1957-1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Rochester- Study of employment practices data, 1950-1960 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Employment agencies and the labor market process in Rochester, NY Manuscript, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Employment Tables, 1947-1953 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Courses for ES Counselors- handbooks, study manuals, ect., 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- The contribution of the Public Employee to labor market organization., 1964 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Labor Force- reprints, reports, 1960-1967 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Labor Market Theory- notes, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- N.Y.S. Dept. of Labor. Labor Market Reports, Workforce estimate, and miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- U.S. Dept. of Labor. Bureau of Employment Security. Data, speeches, reports., 1953-1966 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Local Office Management, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- War Production Drive Labor-Management Production Committees in New York and New Jersey, 1943-1945 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Public Employment Service in the U.S., 1963 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Notes, bibliography, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Employment Agencies and Manpower Policies. Manuscripts and Draft., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Employment Agencies and Manpower Policies. Draft., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Arizona- Employee Service Operations, 1955-1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Arizona- Private Agencies, 1959-1962 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Employment Agencies and he Labor Marketing Forces in Phoenix, Arizona, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Arizona- Employment and Labor Force Turnover, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Arizona- Phoenix, Tucson- Employment stations of applicants, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- California- Private agencies, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Arizona- General Business Conditions, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Arizona- Employee Services. Legislation and Organizing, 1949-1962 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- California- notes, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- San Francisco- Employment Services, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- California- Background material., 1950-1961 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Otsego, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Tioga, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Chenago, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Delaware County, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Broome, 1959-1964 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Five County Area Vocational Education Study. Plans and data., 1964 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Public Youth Employment Service in San Francisco- draft, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Manuscripts. Calif. Background material, data, notes, ect., 1960-1962 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Chenango- data, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Broome- data, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Otsego- data, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Five County Area Vocational Education Study Data- Delaware, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Tioga- data, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Broome, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Employment agencies and the labor marketing process in San Francisco, California, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Governor's Committee on Public Employee Relations, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Farm labor project, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Adams, L.P., How B., Warson, O.I. Worker management relationships on farms in N..S. in 1966: a study based on selected classes., 1966- 1967 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Farm labor study- final report, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Adams, L.P., How, B. Larson, O.F. Worker management relationships on farms in N.Y.S. in 1966 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Viable Farmer-Worker Relationships: A Study of Selected Cases in New York States in 1966 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Worker-Management Relationships on Farms in New York State in 1966, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Retyped pages from edited edition, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Farm Labor Projects, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Farm labor study- case material, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Farm Labor Background Material, 1964-1967 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Labor force- migratory farm workers, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Labor force- migratory farm workers, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 13)